<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work with Diagrams on Markdown Presentations for Developers</title>
    <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work with Diagrams on Markdown Presentations for Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>

	<atom:link href="https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title>Sketch Whiteboard</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/sketch-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/sketch-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>The Excalidraw whiteboard lets you quickly sketch any diagram with a hand-drawn feel. Ideal for sharing mockups, wireframes, system diagrams, UI workflows, casual brainstorming, concepts, and more. You can save your sketches as pixel-perfect SVG or PNG for rendering on any slide.
The whiteboard is powered by the amazing Excalidraw Sketch Tool and integrated seamlessly for working offline within GitPitch Desktop. For details see the Desktop Whiteboard Guide .</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Cloud Diagram Widget</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/cloud-diagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/cloud-diagrams/</guid>
      <description>Activate a GitPitch Paid Plan to unlock Cloud Diagram Widget support.
 This guide describes the @cloud widget. This widget is a simple markdown syntax that can be used to create and render sophisticated cloud system architecture diagrams powered by Diagrams-As-Code on any slide.
 Cloud Widget Usage Conventions  Cloud Diagrams Image Manipulations  Learn By Example - AWS Event Processing  More Examples in the Diagrams-As-Code Docs    Click here to experience Cloud Diagrams live in a sample GitPitch slide deck.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Mermaid Diagram Widget</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/mermaid-diagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/mermaid-diagrams/</guid>
      <description>Activate a GitPitch Paid Plan to unlock UML Diagram Widget support.
 This guide describes the @mermaid widget. This widget is a simple markdown syntax that can be used to render Mermaid Diagrams and Flowcharts on any slide.
 Mermaid Widget Usage Conventions  Mermaid Diagrams Built-In Themes  Mermaid Diagrams Image Manipulations  Mermaid Diagrams Background Colors  Mermaid Diagrams Layout Orientation  Learn By Example - Flowchart  Learn By Example - Flowchart Styling  Learn By Example - Sequence Diagram  More Examples in the Mermaid Docs   Mermaid Widget Usage Conventions Each diagram is defined using a simple text-based syntax within a dedicated description file.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UML Diagram Widget</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/uml-diagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/uml-diagrams/</guid>
      <description>Activate a GitPitch Paid Plan to unlock UML Diagram Widget support.
 This guide describes the @uml widget. This widget is a simple markdown syntax that can be used to render PlantUML diagrams on any slide.
 UML Widget Usage Conventions  UML Diagrams Image Manipulations  UML Diagrams Layout Orientation  Learn By Example - Sequence Diagrams  Learn By Example - Activity Diagrams  Learn By Example - State Diagrams  Learn By Example - Timing Diagrams  Learn By Example - Use Case Diagrams  Learn By Example - Object Diagrams  More Examples in the PlantUML Docs    Click here to experience UML Diagrams live in a sample GitPitch slide deck.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Graphviz/DOT Diagrams</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/graphviz-diagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/graphviz-diagrams/</guid>
      <description>Activate a GitPitch Paid Plan to unlock Graphviz/Dot Diagrams.
 The UML Widget powered by PlantUML makes use of Graphviz/DOT Visualization Software for rendering under the hood. This guide describes how you can leverage Graphviz/Dot support directly to generate sophisticated graphs on any slide.
 Graphviz/Dot Usage Conventions  Learn by Example - A  Learn by Example - B  Learn by Example - C  Learn by Example - D  Graphviz/Dot Diagrams GitPitch Caching Policy   Graphviz/Dot Widget Usage Conventions The conventions required to use Graphviz/Dot diagrams are as follows:</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Line Bar Radar Charts</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/diagram-features/charts/</guid>
      <description>Add beautifully rendered line, bar, pie, radial, etc. charts to any slide. Support for charts within GitPitch slide decks is powered by the Reveal.js plugin for Chart.js .
 Learn by Example - Line Chart  Learn By Example - Bar Chart  Learn By Example - Radar Chart  Charts Plugin Activation   By default, this plugin is disabled. To enable this plugin for your presentation, see Charts Plugin Activation below.</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>