<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work with Math on Markdown Presentations for Developers</title>
    <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/docs/math-features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work with Math on Markdown Presentations for Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>

	<atom:link href="https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/docs/math-features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title>MathJax Formulas</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/docs/math-features/math-formulas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/docs/math-features/math-formulas/</guid>
      <description>Add beautifully rendered math formulas to any slideshow presentation using the following:
 MathJax Support or LaTeX &amp;#43; AsciiMath Widget   This guide documents MathJax Support via the MathJax plugin. MathJax is a JavaScript display engine for mathematics with support for LaTeX, MathML and other equation markup.
By default, this plugin is disabled. To enable this plugin for your presentation, see MathJax plugin activation .
 Learn By Example  Learn By Example within Snap Layouts  MathJax Plugin Activation  MathJax Backticks Syntax  LaTeX &amp;#43; AsciiMath Widget   Learn By Example This PITCHME.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>LaTeX &#43; AsciiMath Widget</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/docs/math-features/latex-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/docs/math-features/latex-math/</guid>
      <description>Activate a GitPitch Paid Plan to unlock LaTeX + AsciiMath Widget support.
  UML Widget for LaTeX &amp;#43; AsciiMath  Learn By Example - LaTeX Math  Learn By Example - Ascii Math   UML Widget for LaTeX + AsciiMath The UML Widget provides some excellent extensions for rendering math formulas on any slide. The same conventions, caching policies, and @uml widget syntax apply. This support is provided as an lightweight alternative to using MathJax Formulas .</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>