<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modular Slideshows on Markdown Presentations for Developers</title>
    <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modular Slideshows on Markdown Presentations for Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>

	<atom:link href="https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title>Unlimited Slideshows</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-many-slideshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-many-slideshows/</guid>
      <description>The PITCHME.md convention guarantees that any PITCHME.md markdown file found within any directory on any branch within your repository can be turned into a GitPitch slideshow presentation.
This guide explains how you can create, manage, and share an unlimited number of slideshow presentations within a single Git repository branch.
 Working with the default Slideshow Presentation within a Branch  Working with additional Slideshow Presentations within a Branch  Example - Conference Slideshow Presentation URL  Example - New York Meetup Slideshow Presentation URL   Working with the default Slideshow Presentation within a Branch The PITCHME.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Slideshow Shared Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-shared-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-shared-assets/</guid>
      <description>The Many Slideshows Guide details the ability of GitPitch to serve an unlimited number of slideshow presentations from within a single Git branch. This guide discusses some of the added advantages of using a single branch in this way.
Specifically, a single branch approach allows for the reuse of a wide range of slideshow assets across multiple presentations. These assets can include images , custom logos , slide backgrounds , and even custom css .</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Modular Markdown</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-shared-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-shared-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Developers are accustomed to writing code in a modular fashion. Modularity is achieved using distinct functions, files, and directories to partition code in meaningful ways. This approach typically improves code clarity and aids modifications and maintenance over time.
GitPitch supports this same modular approach for presentation markdown and associated image assets, settings, and custom css.
 Learn By Example  The Modular Markdown Slide Delimiter  Example: Modular HTML5 Training Slideshow  Example: Modular Localized Slideshow Content  Example: Modular Audience Specific Slideshow Content   1.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Modular Slideshows</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-modular-slideshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/git/branch-modular-slideshows/</guid>
      <description>The Modular Markdown Guide details the recommended approach and key benefits of adopting a modular design when developing and managing slideshow presentation content. Especially when you are developing course or training materials.
This guide takes modularity one step further, showing you how you can use modular markdown to deliver modular slideshows.
 What is a Modular Slideshow?  Example: HTML5 Training Slideshow Revisited  Example: HTML5 Training Mini-Slideshows  Example: The GitPitch Demo Deck   What is a Modular Slideshow?</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>