<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work with Images on Markdown Presentations for Developers</title>
    <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work with Images on Markdown Presentations for Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Inline Images</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/inline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/inline/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example  Inline Local Image Files  Inline External Image Files   Any JPEG, PNG, or GIF image can be displayed inline on any slide using standard Markdown image syntax. For a quick reference on standard Markdown image syntax see the Mastering Markdown Guide .
 SVG support for pixel perfect rendering at any resolution is a Pro image feature .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inline Image Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/image-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/image-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Activate a GitPitch Paid Plan to unlock Inline Image Manipulation support.
 This guide introduces powerful image-manipulation techniques that can be applied to inline images on any slide.
 Image Sizing  Image Opacity  Image Filters  Image 2D Transformations  Image 3D Transformations  Image Fragment Behaviour  Image Custom Styles  Image Alt Text  Image Title Text      For even more image manipulation features see the Background Images Guide .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Images</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/background/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example  Image Delimiter Syntax - Local Image Files  Image Delimiter Syntax - External Image Files  Image Delimiter Syntax - Power Features   Basic slide delimiter syntax allows markdown content to be split into a series of slides. Special image delimiter syntax allows overriding the basic delimiter semantics in order to display any JPEG, PNG, or GIF image as a background image on specific slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Scaling</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/scaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/scaling/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example  Image Delimiter Scaling Syntax - Contain Image  Image Delimiter Scaling Syntax - Cover Image  Image Delimiter Scaling Syntax - Fit Tall Image  Image Delimiter Scaling Syntax - Squeeze Image   Image delimiter syntax supports a size parameter that gives you complete control over background image sizing and scaling.
The size paramter can take any value that is valid on the background-size css property .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Positioning</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/positioning/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example   Image delimiter syntax supports a position parameter that gives you complete control over background image positioning within slides.
The position paramter can take any value that is valid on the background-position css property . These values include center, left, right, 25% 75%, bottom 50px right 100px, etc.
If the position parameter is not specified, the default position value for background images is center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Colors</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/colors/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example   Image delimiter syntax supports a color parameter that gives you the ability to change the color of the exposed area of a slide background for an individual slide.
By default, the background color for any slide is determined by the active slideshow theme . Using the color parameter you can change the background color to a custom value for an individual slide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Repeat</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/repeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/repeat/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example   Image delimiter syntax supports a repeat parameter that gives you the ability to have a background image repeated on a slide background.
By default, background images are rendered with a no-repeat pattern. The repeat paramter can take any value that is valid on the background-repeat css property .
Learn By Example This PITCHME.md markdown snippet:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Animations</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/animations/</guid>
      <description>Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
 Learn By Example   Consecutive image delimiters can be used to create an seamless animation effect using a series of related background images.
To achieve a fluid animation, the slide transition setting - for the entire presentation or for the individual slides participating in the animation - must be set to none.
Learn By Example This PITCHME.md markdown snippet:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Background Opacity</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/opacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/opacity/</guid>
      <description>GitPitch Paid Plans activate the Background Image Opacity feature.
  Learn By Example   Important! Remember to size-optimize your presentation images for the Web.
Image delimiter syntax supports an opacity parameter that gives you the ability to apply opacity filters to individual background images.
By default, background images are 100% opaque. Reducing the opacity level from 100 increases the transparency of a background image. The more transparent a slide background image, the more other content on the slide - such as text content - stands out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Size Limits</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/size-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/image-features/size-limits/</guid>
      <description>Offline Image Size Limits  Online Image Size Limits   Offline Image Size Limits By default, GitPitch Desktop enforces the same image sizes limits as those enforced when publishing slide decks online :
However, the Desktop also includes the following features:
 A PITCHME.yaml setting that allows you to disable image size limits for any deck A built-in image compression tool that identifies and compresses oversized images  For details about these Desktop features, see the Desktop Image Tools Guide .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>