<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitPitch CI Guide on Markdown Presentations for Developers</title>
    <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitPitch CI Guide on Markdown Presentations for Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GitPitch CI Intro</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/intro/</guid>
      <description>Introduction GitPitch CI is delivered as a Docker image. This image can be used as an executor within your CI/CD pipeline to generate PDF, PPTX, and/or JPG screenshots for slide decks found in any Git repository.
Like any CI/CD pipeline job, GitPitch CI can be launched in response to typical events such as a commit, tag, or release on target branches and repositories.
The steps to activate GitPitch CI within your pipeline are dependent on your CI/CD provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch on CircleCI</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/circleci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/circleci/</guid>
      <description>GitPitch CI on CircleCI  GitPitch CI Environment Variables  GitPitch CI Sample Generated Artifacts  GitPitch CI Persist To CircleCI Workspace  GitPitch CI Persist As CircleCI Artifacts   GitPitch CI Environment Variables The behavior of GitPitch CI at runtime depends on the values set for the following required environment variables:
 $GITPITCHCI_TARGET - identifies the target slide deck or decks within the target reposistory for processing $GITPITCHCI_TYPE - identifies the type of file artifacts to be generated by GitPitch CI for the target slide deck or decks $DOCKERHUB_USER - identifies the name of the Docker Hub account that has beeen granted access to GitPitch CI $DOCKERHUB_PASS - identifies the password of the Docker Hub account that has beeen granted access to GitPitch CI  The $GITPITCHCI_TARGET environment variable takes the following values:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch on GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitpitch.com/docs/ci/github-actions/</guid>
      <description>GitPitch CI on GitHub Actions Details coming soon. If you are interested in using GitPitch CI within your GitHub Actions pipelines please get in touch .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>