<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enterprise Guide on Markdown Presentations for Developers</title>
    <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enterprise Guide on Markdown Presentations for Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>

	<atom:link href="https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Licensing</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/license/</guid>
      <description>GitPitch Enterprise License An Enterprise license unlocks both the GitPitch Server and GitPitch Desktop .
The Enterprise license is made available on a recurring subscription basis. Yearly and quarterly subscription plans are available. Pricing details are available on the GitPitch website, see here .</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Features</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/features/</guid>
      <description>Features GitPitch Enterprise delivers a modified version of the production software used on gitpitch.com . Please note the following feature differences exist between the gitpitch.com server and the GitPitch Enterprise server:
Publishing via Private Repos The GitPitch Enterprise server can be used to publish slideshow presentations from both public and private repositories managed by your self-hosted Git servers. However, the stealth and confidential mode publishing features on gitpitch.com are not supported by the GitPitch Enterprise server.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Deployment Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>Deployment Prerequisites GitPitch Enterprise must be deployed as a Docker container running in a Linux server environment. The GitPitch Enterprise container depends on a Docker volume at runtime. This volume is used:
 To pass custom GitPitch server configuration to the live container. To cache GitPitch server log data outside of the live container. To cache GitPitch server runtime data outside of the live container.  For on-premises deployment, the Docker volume is typically a dedicated directory on your host Linux server.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Install GitPitch Enterprise</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/install/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Getting Started  Step 2. Install Docker  Step 3. Create Docker Hub Account  Step 4. Register your Docker Hub ID  Step 5. Await Access Confirmation  Step 6. Login To Docker Hub  Step 7. Pull GitPitch Enterprise Image  Step 8. Verify GitPitch Enterprise Image   Step 1. Getting Started If you have not activated a trial subscription for GitPitch Enterprise you can do so now on the GitPitch website, click here .</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Launch GitPitch Enterprise</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/launch/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Verify GitPitch Enterprise Docker Image  Step 2. Prepare GitPitch Server Test Configuration  Step 3. Prepare GitPitch Server Log Configuration  Step 4. Prepare Docker Volume Directory  Step 5. Test Launch GitPitch Enterprise  Step 6. Verify Test Launch GitPitch Enterprise  Step 7. Prepare GitPitch Server Production Configuration  Step 8. Launch GitPitch Enterprise  Step 9. Verify Launch GitPitch Enterprise  Appendix - Interactive v Detached Mode Launch   Step 1.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Config GitPitch Enterprise</title>
      <link>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://www.devlead.se/docs-30/enterprise/config/</guid>
      <description>Server Log Production Configuration  Server Log Debug Configuration  Activate Personal Access Tokens  HTTPS/SSL Certificate Configuration  HTTPS/SSL Using PEM Certificates  HTTPS/SSL Using JKS Certificates   Server Log Production Configuration The following production log configuration instructs the GitPitch server to write all log statements to a file called gitpitch-server-production.log in your Docker volume directory. Logging to standard out is disabled.
&amp;lt;configuration&amp;gt; &amp;lt;conversionRule conversionWord=&amp;quot;coloredLevel&amp;quot; converterClass=&amp;quot;play.api.libs.logback.ColoredLevel&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;appender name=&amp;quot;FILE&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ch.</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>